Exhibition Records, 1983-1994
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Exhibition Records
1983-1994
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
National Portrait Gallery, Office of Exhibitions
SI Records
8 cu. ft. (8 record storage boxes)
Accession 98-139
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of records pertaining to the planning and development of nine exhibitions ("Blessed Are the Peacemakers;" "U.S. Grant: The Man and the Image;" "Portraits by Brady: Imperial Photographs from the Harvard College Library;" "Noble Heritage: Five Centuries of Portraits from the Hosokawa Family;" "The Spirit of the Party: Hamilton and Jefferson at Odds;" "In Pursuit of Fame: Rembrandt Peale, 1778-1860;" "White City: American Art at the 1893 World Fair;" "From Elizabeth I to Elizabeth II: Master Drawings from the National Portrait Gallery, London;" and "Contemporary Self-Portraits from the James Goode Collection"). Materials include checklists, scripts, labels, loan agreements, correspondence, memoranda, lender sheets, funding and budget information, photographs, and research notes.
Access Restriction
Box 8 contains materials restricted indefinitely; see finding aid. Contact reference staff for details.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Peale, Rembrandt, 1778-1860; American Art at the 1893 World's Fair (Exhibition) (1993: Washington, D.C.); Blessed Are the Peacemakers (Exhibition) (1983: Washington, D.C.); Contemporary Self-Portraits from the James Goode Collection (Exhibition) (1993: Washington, D.C.); From Elizabeth I to Elizabeth II: Master Drawings from the National Portrait Gallery, London (Exhibition) (1994: Washington, D.C.); In Pursuit of Fame: Rembrandt Peale, 1778-1860 (Exhibition) (1992-1993: Washington, D.C.); Noble Heritage: Five Centuries of Portraiture from the Hosokawa Family (Exhibition) (1992: Washington, D.C.); Portraits by Brady: Imperial Photographs from the Harvard College Library (Exhibition) (1986: Washington, D.C.); Spirit of the Party: Hamilton and Jefferson at Odds (Exhibition) (1992: Washington, D.C.); U.S. Grant: The Man and the Image (Exhibition) (1985: Washington, D.C.)
Subject
Art museums.; Exhibitions
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Manuscripts; Black-and-white photographs
- Box 1
  - Blessed are the Peace Makers - September 3 to November 27, 1983
  - Lender Sheets (Box 1 of 8)
  - Script (Box 1 of 8)
  - General (Box 1 of 8)
  - Treaty of Paris (September '83) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Manuscript copies of Treaty Labels (Box 1 of 8)
  - Funding and Budget (Box 1 of 8)
  - Catalogue Manuscript (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Lady Teresa Agnew (Charles James Fox by Joshua Reynolds) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - American Philosophical Society (5 items) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - The Art Museum, Princeton University (Elkanah Watson by John Singleton Copley) - denied (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Boston Public Library (library medal) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Castle, Mrs. J. Manderson Jr. (William Franklin by Mather Brown) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - William Clements Library (1782 Broadside written by B. Franklin in Passy) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Cleveland Museum of Art (Geore III by Benjamin West) - Not lending (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Colonial Williamsburg (The Reconcilliation between Britania...) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Columbia University (David Hartley by George Romney) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Columbia University (Ms S. Jay's toast, John Jay's diplomatic code book) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Earl if Powis (John Strachey by unidentified artist) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Fogg Art Museum (John Adams by John Singleton Copley) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Gilcrease Museum (William Temple Franklin by Mather Brown) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Henry Francis du Pont Winterthur Museum (The Peacemakers by Benjamin West) - Denied (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Her Majesty the Queen of England (George III by Thomas Gainsborough) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - City of Coventry Herbert Art Gallery Museum(George III by Lawrence) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Historical Society of Pennsylvania (two broadsides re: the Treaty celeb.) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Dr. Mrs. Alvin M. Kanter (Wedgwood medallion of William Franklin) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Library of Congress (8 items) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Lafayette College (Marquis de Lafayette by Jean Baptiste Le Paon) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - The Marquess of Lansdowne (Lord Shelburne by Mosnier) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Massachusetts Historical Society (passport form for Amers. By J. Adams) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Correspondence with the Minnesota Historical Society (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Musee de Versailles Trianon (Comte de Vergennes by unid, Louis XVI by Duplessis) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Museo del Prado (Conde de Florida-blanca by Goya Carlos III by Mengs) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - National Archives (British Treaty, Swedish Treaty) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - National Gallery of Art (Chateau de Valentinois, Passy att. To Perignon) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - National Museum of American History (Candlesticks used in the room where the Treaty was signed) - Denied (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - National Portrait Gallery (Lauren by Copley, Jay by Stuart?, Adams by Trumbull) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - The New-York Historical Society (Adams by Vinkels, Livingston by Stuart, Mit. map) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Portrait of Oswald (as of yet, not located) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Portrait of State (Desk at which the treaty was signed.) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - United States Air Force Academy (2 pieces) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Yale University Library (Benjamin Franklin by Joseph Wright) (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Washington Irving Commemorative - April 2 through September 25, 1983 (Box 1 of 8)
  - Lender - Washington Irving (Box 1 of 8)
- Box 2
  - U. S. Grant: The Man and the Image - July 23 to November 11, 1985
  - General (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lender Sheets (Box 2 of 8)
  - The Man The Image (Box 2 of 8)
  - Photo Orders (Box 2 of 8)
  - Wall Case Label, Xeroxes (Box 2 of 8)
  - Correspondence with Lyndon B. Johnson (LBJ) Library (Box 2 of 8)
  - Catalogue (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Addison Gallery of American Art (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Chicago Historical Society (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Detroit Historical Museum (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Dimock Gallery (George Washington University) (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Galena Historical Museum (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Gelman Library (George Washington University) (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Illinois State Historical Library (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Library of Congress (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Mark Twain Memorial (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Missouri Historical Society (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - The National Archives (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Portrait Gallery - SI (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Museum of American History (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Ohio Historical Society (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - The Players -Drop (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Mr Mrs Jeffrey Slobodian (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Stratford Hall (R. E. Lee Memorial Assiciation) (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Sally Turner Gallery (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - Union League of Philadelphia (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - West Point Museum (Box 2 of 8)
  - Lenders - The White House (Box 2 of 8)
  - Portraits by Brady: Imperial Photographs from the Harvard College Library - April 25 to August 24, 1986
  - Research Photos (Box 2 of 8)
  - Salt Prints April 1986 (Box 2 of 8)
  - Label Manuscript (Box 2 of 8)
  - Xerox Copies (Box 2 of 8)
  - Loans from the Harvard University Art Museum (Box 2 of 8)
- Box 3
  - Noble Heritage: Five Centuries of Portrait from the Hosokawa Family - July 24 to November 29, 1992
  - Loan Negotiations (Box 3 of 8)
  - Opening (Box 3 of 8)
  - Publicity (Box 3 of 8)
  - Jared Lubarsky (Box 3 of 8)
  - General (Box 3 of 8)
  - Catalogue (Box 3 of 8)
  - Conservation (Box 3 of 8)
  - Education (Box 3 of 8)
  - Funding (Box 3 of 8)
  - Indemnity (Box 3 of 8)
  - Labels (Box 3 of 8)
  - Photographs (Box 3 of 8)
- Box 4
  - The Spirit of the Party: Hamilton and Jefferson at Odds - September 11, 1992 to February 7, 1993
  - General (Box 4 of 8)
  - National Portrait Gallery (NPG) (Box 4 of 8)
  - Jefferson Birthday Celebration (Box 4 of 8)
  - Catalogue (Box 4 of 8)
  - Catalogue Illustrations (Box 4 of 8)
  - Deinstallation (Box 4 of 8)
  - Education (Box 4 of 8)
  - Funding (Box 4 of 8)
  - Labels (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lender Sheets (Box 4 of 8)
  - Opening (Box 4 of 8)
  - Photo Panel (Box 4 of 8)
  - Printouts (Box 4 of 8)
  - Publicity (Box 4 of 8)
  - Resident Associates Program Course (Box 4 of 8)
  - Script (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Albany Institute of History and Art (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - American Antiquarian Society (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Baltimore Museum of Art (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Colonial Williamsburg (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Duke University (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Gibbes Museum of Art (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Historical Society of Pennsylvania (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Independence National Historical Park (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Library Company of Philadelphia (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Library of Congress (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - A Theodore Lyman (on loan to the Essex Institute) (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Massachusetts Historical Society (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Archives (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - New Jersey Historical Society (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - New York Historical Society (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - New York Public Library (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Olney, Mr. Peter (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Rush, Mr. Lockwood (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Yale University (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Bowdoin College - Dropped/Denied (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Donaldson, Lufkin Jenrette, Inc. - Withdrawn November 7, 1991 (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston - Denied (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Gallery of Art - Denied (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Wocester Art Museum - Withdrawn, Cat. Illustration (Box 4 of 8)
  - Lenders - Atwater Kent Museum - Withdrawn (Box 4 of 8)
  - Research (Box 4 of 8)
  - Manuscript (Box 4 of 8)
  - Labels (Box 4 of 8)
- Box 5
  - In Pursuit of Fame: Rembrandt Peale, 1778-1860 - November 6, 1992 to February 7, 1993
  - General (Box 5 of 8)
  - Brochure (Box 5 of 8)
  - Publicity (Box 5 of 8)
  - Catalogue Illustration (Box 5 of 8)
  - Catalogue/Book (Box 5 of 8)
  - Computer Printout (Box 5 of 8)
  - Deinstallation (Box 5 of 8)
  - Education (Box 5 of 8)
  - Funding/Development (Box 5 of 8)
  - Carol Hevner, Co-curator (Box 5 of 8)
  - Label Manuscripts (Box 5 of 8)
  - Label Typesets (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lender Sheets (Box 5 of 8)
  - Objects Received (Box 5 of 8)
  - Opening (Box 5 of 8)
  - Photography to be returned (Box 5 of 8)
  - Research (Box 5 of 8)
  - Script (Box 5 of 8)
  - Script - Primary Lists (Box 5 of 8)
  - Illus. Lists (Box 5 of 8)
  - Private Owners - Contract Photography (Box 5 of 8)
  - Catalogue Images - In order (Box 5 of 8)
  - Wall Labels (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - American Art Portrait Gallery Library (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Academy of Natural Science of Philadelphia (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - American Antiquarian Society (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - American Philosophical Society Library (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Art Institute of Chicago (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Atwater Kent Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Baltimore City Life Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Bentley, Fred D., Sr. (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Bishop Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Bley Bley (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Boston Athenaeum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Brooklyn Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Chrysler Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Corcoran Gallery of Art (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Davis, Diana - 1 venue only (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Detroit Institute of Arts (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - El Paso Museum of Art (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Ford, Christopher Peale (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Gibbes Museum of Art (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Gray, Mr. John Chipman, III (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Eisenhower Library, Johns Hopkins (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Harvard University Art Museums (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Historical Society of Pennsylvania (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Houghton Library (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Independence National Historical Park (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Kinsolving, Henrietta Maria Littlefield, Anne Davidson (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Kyte, Mr. Lawrence H., Jr. (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Library of Congress (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Lindstrom, Mr. Mrs. James (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Los Angeles County Museum of Art (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Lowe Art Museum, University of Miami (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Manney Collection (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Maryland Historical Society (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Mead Art Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Medical and Chirurgical Faculty (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Meslans, Maurice R. (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Montclair Art Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Gallery of Art (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Museum of American Art (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Portrait Gallery (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Newark Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - New-York Historical Society (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Pennsylvania Academy of The Fine Arts (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Philadelphia Museum of Art (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Pierpont Morgan Library (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Princeton University (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Rockefeller, Mrs. Rodman C. (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Thomas Root (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Smith, Mrs. Dean Day, c/o White, Virginia and Edward L. White (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Smithsonian Institution Library (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Stenberg, Jo Ann (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Supreme Court of the United States (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - John H. Surovek Gallery (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - United States Senate (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Walters Art Gallery (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - White House (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Winterthur Museum (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Wadsworth Atheneum - Denied (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Muscarelle Museum of Art - Denied (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Boston Public Library - Withdrawn (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Rah, Jason Associates / Boykin, Mary - Denied, illustration only (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Hagley Museum and Library - Denied (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Hoge, Mrs. George - Denied (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Ford, F. Richards - Denied, illustration only (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Preston, Miss Janet C. - Denied, illustration only (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Sotheby's - Drop (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Trump, Mr. and Mrs. Robert - Withdrawn, illustration only (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Traveling Exhibit - R. Peale - Withdrawn (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - New-York Historical Society Traveling Exhibition - Withdrawn (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Gibbes Art Museum Traveling Exhibition - Withdrawn (Box 5 of 8)
  - Lenders - Miles L. Wardlaw - Illustration only (Box 5 of 8)
- Box 6
  - White City: American Art at the 1893 World Fair - April 16 to August 15, 1993
  - 1893 (1993) (Box 6 of 8)
  - Brochure (Box 6 of 8)
  - Catalogue (Box 6 of 8)
  - Education (Box 6 of 8)
  - Funding (Box 6 of 8)
  - Label Typesets (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lender Sheets (Box 6 of 8)
  - Publicity (Box 6 of 8)
  - Script (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Addison Gallery (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Amon Carter Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Art Institute of Chicago (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Berkshire Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Berry-Hill Galleries, Inc. for the Raethers (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Brooklyn Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Carnegie Museum of Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Chesterwood (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Clark Art Institute (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - First Unitarian Church (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Galleries of Claremont College (Scripps Collage) (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Cleveland Public Library (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Columbian Club Foundation (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Columbus Museum of Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Conant, Mrs. Sally Lorensen (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Corcoran Gallery of Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Couse, Mr. Irving W. (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Mrs. John T. Cumbler (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Danforth Museum of Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Deutsches Historisches Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Duquesne Club (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Fine Arts Museum of San Francisco, M. H. de Young Memorial Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Finn, Mr. and Mrs. Joel (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Fraad, Daniel (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Freeman, Mr. John W. (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Richard Green / England (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Gulf States Paper Corp. (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Harvard University Law Library (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Hoyt, Mrs. Malcolm (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Hull-House, Jane Addam's (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Thomas Jefferson University (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Herbert F. Johnson Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Los Angeles County Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Louisville Free Public Library (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - McMullen, Dr. John J. (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Manney, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Montclair Art Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Museo de Arte de Ponce (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Museum Fine Arts, Springfield (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Museum of American Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - National Portrait Gallery (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - New Britain Museum American Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Northwestern University Library (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Philadelphia Museum of Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Phillips Collection (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Relfe, Mrs. Genelle (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Rhode Island School of Design (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Rosse, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Salem Country Historical Society (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Ira Spanierman Gallery (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Staten Island Institute Of Arts Sciences (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Sheldon Swope Museum (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Tate Gallery of Art / London (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Tennessee Wesleyan College (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Terra Museum of American Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Timkin Museum of Art (Box 6 of 8)
  - Lenders - Union League Club of Chicago (Box 6 of 8)
- Box 7
  - Lenders - U.S. Naval Academy Museum (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - University Club (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - University of California (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Utah Museum of Fine Arts (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Valparaiso University Museum of Art (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Wadsworth Atheneum (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Walters Art Gallery (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Washington and Lee University (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Weibel, Jay (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Wellesley College Art Museum (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Whittle Communications/ Christopher Whittle (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Willford, Graham (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Richard York Gallery (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - R. W. Norton Gallery - Denied (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - The Century Club - Dropped (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Mr. Charles W. McCutchen - Dropped (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - St. Vincent Medical Center - Dropped (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Columbian Expo Loan Rejection Letters (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Luce Foundation (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - New Jersey State Museum - Dropped (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Oakland Museum - No (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Portland Art Museum - Denied (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - New-York Historical Society - Denied (Box 7 of 8)
  - Lenders - Jordon-Volpe Gallery - Not in exhibition (Box 7 of 8)
- Box 8
  - From Elizabeth I to Elizabeth II: Master Drawings from the National Portrait Gallery, London - January 1 to May 24, 1994
  - Portrait Drawings (Box 8 of 8)
  - ASI Contract (Box 8 of 8)
  - Brochure (Box 8 of 8)
  - Education (Box 8 of 8)
  - Funding (Box 8 of 8)
  - Opening (Box 8 of 8)
  - Publicity (Box 8 of 8)
  - PR Photos from Warren Associates (Box 8 of 8)
  - Labels (Box 8 of 8)
  - Typeset Labels (Box 8 of 8)
  - Contemporary Self-Portraits from the James Goode Collection - July 30 to December 5, 1993
  - Collection (Box 8 of 8)
  - Illustration permissions (Box 8 of 8)
  - Labels (Box 8 of 8)
  - Typeset Labels (Box 8 of 8)
  - Catalogue (Box 8 of 8)
  - Opening (Box 8 of 8)
  - Publicity (Box 8 of 8)
  - Photographs (Box 8 of 8)
  - Interpretations (Box 8 of 8)
  - Bibliography - Research (Box 8 of 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8 of 8)
  - RESTRICTED FILES
  - RESTRICTED MATERIALS - Non-Circulating (Box 8 of 8)